freewebmonitoring.com 2006-12-31

# Free Web Monitoring: Your Free Web Site Monitoring Service

**Privacy Policy Overview**

This Privacy Policy covers the Free Web Monitoring treatment of personal information that is recorded when you sign-up for our free web site monitoring service. 

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the Free Web Monitoring web site, nor does it extend to people that Free Web Monitoring does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

Unlike many web site monitoring services that charge for web site monitoring and collect personal information as well, Free Web Monitoring is a free service. The only information collected during sign-up is Name, Email Address, URL and IP address. 

Your use of Free Web Monitoring's web site monitoring service constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a business service for your web site(s). In exchange, Free Web Monitoring reserves the right to use the contact information collected during sign up to provide our free newsletter included with your weekly statistics, to deliver email alerts, to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to inform you of additions to the GreenWave Online Network of web sites, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information on behalf of our partners or advertisers. 

With the exception of auto-response messages which are sent when you sign-up for our free web site monitoirng service and contain important account information, you may remove yourself from all email alerts, notices and announcements using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes at least 2 methods to remove yourself from future mailings. **Please note, when you unsubscribe you will be removing your Free Web Monitoring membership and web site monitoring service.** Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact: inquiry[at]freewebmonitoring.com. Our turnaround time for responding to unsubscribe requests is generally 24 hours. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Free Web Monitoring maintains your email address and other pertinent personal information, provided at the time of your sign-up, on the premises. Free Web Monitoring does not rent or sell email addresses nor any other personal data. 

**Cookies**

At this time, cookies are not used on the Free Web Monitoring site. 

**Security**

Your personal information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to Free Web Monitoring staff. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Free Web Monitoring may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

Questions or suggestions may be sent to: inquiry[at]freewebmonitoring.com
